Dorothy Dehner
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1927-1987, Series 2:; (Boxes 1-4; 2.6 linear feet)
  - D (Box 1)
    - (Reel 1372), 1960, 1970, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 120)
    - (unfilmed), 1969-1983 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Martha and LeRoy Davidson (UCLA) (Box 1)
    - (Reel D298), 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 122)
    - (unfilmed), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Maryetta [Davidson] (unfilmed), 1961, 1972-1974, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Holly Day (unfilmed), 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Department of State (Art in Embassies Program) (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - (Reel 796), 1967-1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - (unfilmed), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Design Corner (Reel D298), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Discovery Art Galleries (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - (Reel 1269), undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - E (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1946, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - (unfilmed), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Editions Alecto Ltd. (Reel D298), 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Edmonton Art Gallery (See also Karen Wilkin) (unfilmed), 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Elvehjem Art Center, University of Wisconsin (Box 2)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - (unfilmed), 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - F (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1946-1966 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - (Reel 796), 1966-1973 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - (Reel 1269), 1969, 1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - (Reel 1372), 1974, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - (unfilmed), 1973, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Fairweather-Hardin Gallery (Reel D298), 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Harriet Febland (Box 2)
    - (Reel 1372), 1971, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - (unfilmed), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - N. Michael Fishman (unfilmed), 1984, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Cleo and James Fitch (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1960-1961, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - (Reel 1269), undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Fogg Art Museum, Harvard University (See also Jane Cone) (Reel D298), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Fort Wayne Museum of Art (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - (Reel 829), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - (Reel 1269), 1974-1975, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - G (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1950-1966 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - (Reel 796), 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - (Reel 1372), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - (unfilmed), 1966, 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Gallery at Hastings-on-Hudson (unfilmed), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Gallery Gemini (unfilmed), 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - General Electric (unfilmed), 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Herbert George (Tracks) (Box 2)
    - (Reel 829), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Thomas George (Reel D298), 1963, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Elinor Graham (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - (unfilmed), 1967-1974 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Cleve Gray (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - (Reel 829), 1968-1970, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - (unfilmed), 1970, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Boris and Bea Greenberg (unfilmed), 1979, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Gres Gallery (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1959-1962, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - (unfilmed), 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Grey Art Gallery, New York University (unfilmed), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Guggenheim Museum (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - (unfilmed), 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - H (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1945, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - (Reel 796), 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - (Reel 1269), 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - (unfilmed), 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Margaret Haggerty (Reel 796), 1967-1968, undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - William Heller (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1966-1967, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - (Reel 829), undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Thomas Hess (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - (Reel 1269), undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Hirshhorn Museum (Box 2)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - (unfilmed), 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Walter Horak (Box 2)
    - (Reel 1372), undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - (unfilmed), 1970, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Robert Hunter (Reel 796), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Elliott Hurwitt (Reel D298), 1962-1966 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - The Hyde Collection (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - (unfilmed), 1984 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - I (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - (unfilmed), 1977, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - J (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1965-1966, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - (unfilmed), 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Jewett Arts Center, Wellesley College (Reel D298), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Johns Hopkins Press (Reel 796), 1967-1971, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 81-82)
  - David Hoyt Johnson (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Virginia Jones (unfilmed), 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Kathleen and Pete Juster (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - (unfilmed), 1967-1973, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - K (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - (Reel 796), 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976, undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - (unfilmed), 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Anita Kahn (unfilmed), 1979-1981 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Keystone Junior College (Reel 796), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Kling Interior Design (Reel 1269), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Rosalind Krauss (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - (Reel 796), 1967-1969, undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - (Reel 1372), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - L (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1966, undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - (Reel 796), 1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - (Reel 829), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - (Reel 1269), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - (Reel 1372), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - (unfilmed), 1971, 1975, 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Susan Laird (Reel 1269), 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Ellen Lawrence (Reel 1269), 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Priscilla [Legett] (The Hyde Collection) (Box 2)
    - (Reel 829), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - (Reel 1269), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - (Reel 1372), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - (unfilmed), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Leonardo (Pergamon Press) (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - (unfilmed), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - David Levy (Box 2)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976, undated (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - (unfilmed), 1975, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 112)
  - Joel Levy (See also Artists for Environment) (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), undated (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - (unfilmed), 1975, undated (Box 2, Folder 114)
  - Lucille and Edgar Levy (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1943-1965, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 115-117)
    - (Reel 829), 1970, undated (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - (unfilmed), 1930s-1950s, (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 119-121)
  - Laurie Lisle (unfilmed), 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 122)
  - Ira Lowe (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1965-1966, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - (unfilmed), 1965-1966, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 124)
  - M (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1961-1966 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - (Reel 796), 1968, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976-1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977, undated (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - (unfilmed), 1965, 1981-1986, undated (Box 2, Folder 129)
  - Mary MacNaughton (unfilmed), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 130)
  - Saul and Dorothy Maloff (Reel 1372), 1968 (Box 2, Folder 131)
  - Ferdinand Mann (Box 2)
    - (Reel 829), undated (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - (unfilmed), undated (Box 2, Folder 133)
  - Stanley Marcus (Box 2)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - (Reel 1372), undated (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - (unfilmed), 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 136)
  - Marian Locks Gallery (Box 2)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - (unfilmed), 1977-1978, undated (Box 2, Folder 139)
  - Joan Marter (Rutgers University) (unfilmed), 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 140)
  - Kay McCampbell (Box 2)
    - (Reel 829), 1967 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - (unfilmed), 1975, undated (Box 2, Folder 142)
  - Judith McCandless (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - (Reel 1372), 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - (unfilmed), 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 145)
  - Miranda McClintic (Hirshhorn Museum) (Box 2)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - (unfilmed), 1978-1982, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 147-148)
  - The Member's Gallery, Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 2)
    - (Reel 796), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - (Reel 1296), 1971 (Box 2, Folder 150)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art (unfilmed), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 151)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute (Reel D298), 1960-1963 (Box 2, Folder 152)
  - Museum of Art, Carnegie Institute (unfilmed), 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 153)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, Boston (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1959-1966 (Box 2, Folder 154)
    - (Reel 1269), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 155)
  - Museum of Modern Art (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1956-1966 (Box 2, Folder 156)
    - (Reel 796), 1963-1971, (2 folders) (Box 2, Folder 157-158)
    - (unfilmed), 1986 (Box 2, Folder 159)
  - N (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1960 (Box 2, Folder 160)
    - (Reel 796), 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 161)
    - (Reel 829), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 162)
    - (Reel 1269), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 163)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 164)
    - (unfilmed), 1972, 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 165)
  - Mary Nash (Box 2)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 166)
    - (unfilmed), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 167)
  - National Association of Women Artists (Box 2)
    - (Reel D298), 1966 (Box 2, Folder 168)
    - (Reel 796), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 169)
    - (Reel 1269), 1977 (Box 2, Folder 170)
    - (unfilmed), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 171)
  - National Collection of Fine Arts (unfilmed), 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 172)
  - Louise Nevelson (Box 3)
    - (Reel 829), 1970s (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - (unfilmed), 1960s, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - North Jersey Cultural Council (Box 3)
    - (Reel 796), 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - (Reel 829), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - (Reel 1269), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - O (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - (Reel 796), 1970, 1972, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - (Reel 1269), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - (unfilmed), undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - P (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1957-1963 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - (Reel 796), 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - (Reel 829), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - (Reel 1269), 1962, unfilmed (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - (Reel 1372), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - (unfilmed), 1979-1986 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Stephen Paine (Reel 796), 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Parson's School of Design (New York WPA Artists Exhibition) (Box 3)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - (unfilmed), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Marion Pease (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1948, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - (Reel 1372), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - (unfilmed), undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Katherine Rich Perlow (unfilmed), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Robert [Peterson?] (Box 3)
    - (Reel 1372), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - (unfilmed), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Philadelphia Art Alliance (Reel D298), 1962 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - The Phillips Collection (unfilmed), 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Carlos Arturo Picon (unfilmed), 1973, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Jean Smith Pond (Reel 1372), 1965-1977, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 28-29)
  - Leona Prasse (Box 3)
    - (Reel 796), 1967, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - (Reel 829), 1974, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - (Reel 1269), undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - The Print Club (unfilmed), 1983 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - R (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1960-1966 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - (Reel 796), 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - (Reel 829), undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - (unfilmed), undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Raymond Burr Galleries (Reel D298), 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Helen Robison (See also Bloomington-Normal Art Association) (unfilmed), 1975, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Charlotte Rubenstein (unfilmed), 1980-1987 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Rutgers University (unfilmed), 1982-1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Ruth White Gallery (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1960 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - (Reel 796), 1967 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - S (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1946-1965 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - (Reel 796), 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - (Reel 829), 1966-1973 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - (Reel 1269), 1974-1977 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - (Reel 1372), 1969-1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - (unfilmed), 1953, 1971-1983, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Lucille Sadwith (Reel 796), 1968 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Werner Schmidt (unfilmed), 1979 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Louis Shaeffer (Reel 1269), 1970s (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Skidmore College (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1948, 1960-1965 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - (Reel 796), 1969, 1972-1973, undated, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 56-57)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - (unfilmed), 1977-1987 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Candida Smith (Box 3)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Catherine Smith (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1950-1966, undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - (Reel 796), 1966-1972, undated, (3 folders) (Box 3, Folder 64-66)
    - (Reel 829), 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - (Reel 1269), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - (unfilmed), 1965, undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - David Smith (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1927-1928, 1944-1947, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 70-71)
    - (Reel 1372), 1927 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - (unfilmed), 1947?-1965 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Golda Smith (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1950-1966, undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - (Reel 796), 1966-1972, undated, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 75-76)
    - (Reel 829), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - (unfilmed), 1974, undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Rebecca Smith (Box 3)
    - (Reel 829), 1974, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - (Reel 1372), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - (unfilmed), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Sara Kathryn Smith (Reel 1296), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - St. Bartholomew's Church (unfilmed), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Stamford Museum and Nature Center (unfilmed), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - State University College at Potsdam (Reel 796), 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - H. Peter Stern (See also Storm King Art Center) (unfilmed), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Storm King Art Center (Box 3)
    - (Reel 796), 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - (Reel 829), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - (Reel 1269), 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - (unfilmed), 1976-1986, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 90-91)
  - The Studio Museum in Harlem (unfilmed), 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Syracuse University (Box 3)
    - (Reel 796), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - (unfilmed), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - T (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1948, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - (Reel 1269), 1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - (unfilmed), 1961, undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Tamarind Lithography Workshop (See also University of New Mexico) (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1963-1965 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - (Reel 796), 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - William Thayer (unfilmed), 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Abby and Stephen Thernstrom (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - (unfilmed), 1974, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Melanie Thernstrom (unfilmed), undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - David Traxel (Box 3)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - (unfilmed), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Judd Tully (unfilmed), 1981-1983 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - The Twining Gallery (unfilmed), 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - U (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - (Reel 796), 1967-1972, undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - University Art Museum, State University of New York at Albany (Box 3)
    - (Reel 1269), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - (unfilmed), 1986, undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - University of Cincinnati (unfilmed), 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - University of New Mexico (See also Tamarind Lithography Workshop) (Box 3)
    - (Reel 1269), 1974-1976 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - (Reel 1372), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - (unfilmed), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - V (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - (unfilmed), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 119)
  - Various, Traveling Show (Reel D298), 1951-1954, (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 120-121)
  - Various, Family (unfilmed), 1957-1965 (Box 3, Folder 122)
  - Various, Condolence Letters (Reel D298), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 123)
  - Various, Great Southwest Industrial Park (Atlanta, GA) (Reel 796), 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 124)
  - Various, Jan Matulka Painting (Reel 796), 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 125)
  - Various, Round-Robin Letter (Reel 829), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 126)
  - Various, Painted Surfaces of David Smith Sculptures (Reel 1296), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - W (Box 3)
    - (Reel D298), 1944-1948, 1962, undated (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - (Reel 796), 1967-1973 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - (Reel 829), 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - (Reel 1269), 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - (Reel 1372), 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - (unfilmed), 1977-1986 (Box 3, Folder 133)
  - Tracy White (Reel 796), undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art (Box 3)
    - (Reel 796), 1968, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - (unfilmed), 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 136)
  - Wichita Art Museum (unfilmed), 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Wichita State University (Reel 1269), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 138)
  - Karen Wilkin (unfilmed), 1982, undated (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - Marian Willard (See also Willard Gallery) (Box 3)
    - (Reel 829), 1967, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - (Reel 1372), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - (unfilmed), 1970, undated (Box 3, Folder 143)
  - Willard Gallery (See also Marian Willard) (Box 4)
    - (Reel D298), 1946-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - (Reel 829), 1953-1970 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - (Reel 1269), 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - (unfilmed), 1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - William Pall Gallery (Reel 1269), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Paula Wisotzki (unfilmed), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Women's Caucus for Art (unfilmed), 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Women's Interart Center (Reel 1296), 1974, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - John Xceron (unfilmed), circa 1937 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Yaddo (Reel 796), 1968, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Zimmerli Art Museum, Rutgers University (unfilmed), 1983-1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Irene ------ (Box 4)
    - (Reel D298), undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - (unfilmed), 1967-1980, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Unidentified Letters (Box 4)
    - (Reel D298), 1949, 1965, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - (Reel 796), 1971-1973, undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - (Reel 1269), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - (unfilmed), 1940s, 1970-1985, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Unidentified Fragment (unfilmed), undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Business and Financial Papers, 1940-1985, Series 3:; (Box 4; 0.3 linear feet)
  Series consists of papers relating to various art and personal business matters and to certain financial matters. Some material is organized loosely into gallery and exhibition files consisting of lists, loan agreement forms, consignment receipts, shipping paperwork, and related material pertaining to galleries that represented Dehner at various points in time (including the Willard Gallery and A. M. Sachs Gallery), organizers of exhibitions (such as American Federation of Art and Associated American Artists), or particular exhibitions (including ones at the Philadelphia Art Alliance in 1962, Editions Alecto, Ltd. in 1964, and the Parsons-Dreyfuss Gallery in 1979). Other material is organized loosely into project files, consisting of printed material and notes pertaining to the Committee for the American Participation in the Triennale and to Dehner's commission for the Great Southwest Industrial Park in Atlanta, Georgia (a project which never ended up happening).
  Material relating to more general art business consists of numerous handwritten and typed lists (of works, art sales, prices, exhibitions, art books donated to Skidmore College Library, etc.); visitor books for unidentified exhibitions in 1957, 1959, 1960, and 1963; shipping and delivery receipts; and handwritten documents authenticating certain David Smith works. Material relating to personal business and financial matters includes property and school tax records for Bolton's Landing; a receipt for payment by David Smith, presumably made to Dehner as part of their separation agreement; and an agreement by Dehner to sell certain sculptures by David Smith that she owned to Samuel Dorsky.
  Business and financial papers are arranged in rough chronological order. Related material can be found amongst correspondence.
  - Tax Records (Reel D298), 1940, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibition Records (Box 4)
    - (Reel D298), circa 1945-1965 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - (Reel 796), 1967 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - (unfilmed), 1967, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Receipt for Payment by David Smith (Reel D298), 1952 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Museum of Modern Art (Reel D298), 1952, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Visitor Books (Reel D298), 1957-1963, (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 25-26)
  - Willard Gallery (See also Price Lists and Lists of Works Exhibited and Sold) (unfilmed), 1957-1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - American Federation of Arts (Reel D298), 1960-1963 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Philadelphia Art Alliance (Box 4)
    - (Reel D298), 1962 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - (unfilmed), 1962 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Shipping and Delivery Receipts (Box 4)
    - (Reel D298), 1962-1966, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - (unfilmed), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Lists (Box 4)
    - Lists of Art Sales (unfilmed), 1963, 1977-1980 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Price Lists and Lists of Work Exhibited and Sold (unfilmed), circa 1966-1985 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - List of Art Books Donated to Skidmore College Library (unfilmed), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - List of David Smith Paintings Owned By Dorothy Dehner (Reel 1269), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - List of Disposition of Certain Art Works (unfilmed), undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Lists of Exhibitions and Photographs (unfilmed), undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - List of Works at Home (unfilmed), undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Mailing Lists (unfilmed), undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous Lists (unfilmed), undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Committee for the American Participation in the Triennale (Reel D298), 1964 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Editions Alecto, Ltd. (Reel D298), 1964 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Great Southwest Industrial Park (Reel D298), circa 1967 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Associated American Artists (Box 4)
    - (Reel 796), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - (Reel 1269), 1974-1976 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - (unfilmed), 1976-1987 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Parsons-Dreyfuss Gallery (See also Price Lists and Lists of Works Exhibited and Sold) (unfilmed), 1979 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - A.M. Sachs Gallery (unfilmed), 1981 (Box 4, Folder 49)